Guide to the Shu Lea Cheang Papers MSS.381
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Email, Images, and Budgets, 2001-2002; cuid28859 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_21)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Notes, Research, Budget (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Promotional Material (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Photographic Slides of the Event in New York City, circa 2002 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Trade Tapes #1-5 -- Event at New York Stock Exchange, circa 2002 (Box 6, Video 381.0155 - 381.0159)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Fields #1-7 -- Garlic Harvest Filming, circa 2002 (Box 21, Video 381.0060 - 381.0066)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Trade #6-12 with Filming at NY Stock Exchange, Tompkins Square Park, and other New York City Locations, circa 2002 (Box 21, Video 381.0067 - 381.0073)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- #13 Seed, circa 2002 (Box 21, Video 381.0074)
- Rockefeller Foundation Media Arts Fellowships Booklet, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Creative Practice in the 21st Century Artists Retreat, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Fluidø (2017) -- Casting Call/Session, Promotional Material (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Unknown Title in Chinese -- Video Recording, May 21, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0015)
- Meeting About Money, June 27, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0031)
- Master -- Dents with Mators, July 28, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0030)
- Performance, ELBL / Mutter on Use, August 18, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0016)
- Shoppers Alert, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Photographs -- Cheang on Trip, Working, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Audio Visual Transmission -- AMMI Proposal, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Asami Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
- 沙河悲歌 (电影剧本，初稿) [Sha He bei ge / Elegy of Shahe (Movie script, first draft)], undated (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
- Notebook -- Notes, Ideas, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Critical Writing -- Chinese Press, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Photographic Images - Cheang Portraits, Performers on Stage and Applying Makeup, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Leopard and Wash 3, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0017)
- YaYa's Tape, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0018)
- Sikay / INS Phone Conversation, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0029)
- Hu Die New Recordings, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0032)
- Jane and Joe Get Hitched / Luv, undated (Box 7, Video 381.0038)
- #5 Chicago, Interview, undated (Box 7, Video 381.0039)
- #3 Congress, undated (Box 7, Video 381.0040)
- Spiral and Dance with Peter. Bubu. Diamonds and OK Girls, undated (Box 7, Video 381.0041)
- With Susan Stryker in Tijuana, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0021)
- 蝶 (琉球大学 5/21) [Butterfly (University of Ryukyus 5/21)] -- Video Recording, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0022)
- James' Home Movie, undated (Box 11, Video 381.0054)
- Jackson -- Edit Master, undated (Box 34, Video 381.0087)
- Odine -- Video Recording, undated (Box 38, Reel 381.0095)
- Monkey King Looked West -- Edited Master, undated (Box 37, Video 381.0098)
- News From Afar with Emile de Antonio, undated (Box 38, Video 381.0109)
- Hanafuda -- Master Edit, undated (Box 39, Video 381.0121)
- Taiwan Video Footage, Black/White -- Produce Market, Bell Ringer, Flowing Water, undated; cuid28837 (Reel 381.0168, Reel 381.0169)
- Two People with Painted Faces, undated; cuid28838 (Reel 381.0170)
- Work Files, undated (Box 33, Disc FA_MSS_381_53 -- FA_MSS_381_60; FA_MSS_381_85)
- Documentation for Wasteland and China Footage reels, Includes separation sheets, cleaning reports, receipts, and punched rolls for reels 381.0090, 381.0091, 381.0092, 381.0093, 381.0094, 381.0160, 381.0161, 381.0162, 381.0163, 381.0164, 381.0165, and 381.0166. (Box 40)